ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files /4283
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Program manuals. (Box 170)
  - There's Supposed to be a Law, 1994 (Box 170, Folder 27)
  - Tomorrow's Work, Today's Decisions Part 1, 1992 (Box 170, Folder 28)
  - Tomorrow's Work, Today's Decisions Part 2, 1992 (Box 170, Folder 29)
  - Training Activity Summary, 1993 (Box 170, Folder 30)
- Program manuals. (Box 171)
  - SHRM Launch Book, 2002 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - SHRM Instructor's Resource Book, 2002 (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - SHRM Program Supplement, 2002 (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - SHRM Program Supplement, 2002 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    Contains CD labeled 'PowerPoint Slides'
  - SHRM Instructor's Program Supplement, 2002 (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - SHRM Application Exercises, 2003 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - SHRM Application Exercises Answer Key, 2003 (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - SHRM Instructor's Module 1, 2003 (Box 171, Folder 8)
  - SHRM Instructor's Module 2, 2003 (Box 171, Folder 9)
  - SHRM Instructor's Module 3, 2003 (Box 171, Folder 10)
  - SHRM Instructor's Module 4, 2003 (Box 171, Folder 11)
  - SHRM Instructor's Module 5, 2003 (Box 171, Folder 12)
  - SHRM Instructor's Module 6, 2003 (Box 171, Folder 13)
  - SHRM Launch Book, 2003 (Box 171, Folder 14)
  - SHRM Instructor's Resource Book, 2003 (Box 171, Folder 15)
  - SHRM Instructor's Module 1, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 16)
  - SHRM Instructor's Module 2, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 17)
  - SHRM Instructor's Module 3, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 18)
  - SHRM Instructor's Module 4, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 19)
  - SHRM Instructor's Module 5, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 20)
  - SHRM Instructor's Module 6, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 21)
  - Steps to Implementing Progressive Discipline (Box 171, Folder 22)
  - Successful Retirement Planning Program Proposal, 1998 (Box 171, Folder 23)
  - Successful Training Techniques for Joint Programs, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 24)
  - Successful Training Techniques for Joint Programs (Box 171, Folder 25)
  - Supervisory Management, 1975 (Box 171, Folder 26)
  - Supervisory Management for Healthcare Organization, 1994 (Box 171, Folder 27)
  - Supervisory Management Program Part 1, 1988 (Box 171, Folder 28)
  - Supervisory Management Program Part 2, 1988 (Box 171, Folder 29)
  - Supervisory Management Program Part 3, 1988 (Box 171, Folder 30)
- Institute for Industry Studies. Fleron, Dir. INCLUDES DVDs. (Box 172)
  - Misc. AIS-CD, 2002 (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Misc. AIS-CD, 2002 (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - Ford AIS-CD Meetings, 2001-2002 (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - Ford AIS-CD Correspondence, 2002 (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - UAW- Ford CD Project, 2002 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Ford AIS CD Project, 2002 (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - Ford Auto Industry Dynamics PP Presentation, 2001 (Box 172, Folder 7)
    12/9/01
  - UAW- Ford Project, Focus on the People, 2002 (Box 172, Folder 8)
  - UAW- Ford CD Project, Time of Our Life, 2002 (Box 172, Folder 9)
  - UAW- Ford CD Project, Counting Work, 2002 (Box 172, Folder 10)
  - Ford AIS CD Project, 2002 (Box 172, Folder 11)
  - UAW- Ford CD Project, From Past to Present, 2002 (Box 172, Folder 12)
  - UAW- Ford CD Project, Global Industrial Relations, 2002 (Box 172, Folder 13)
  - UAW- Ford AIS Emails, 2001 (Box 172, Folder 14)
  - Ford AIS Tour Test CD's (Box 172, Folder 15)
    CD's Labeled: 1C, Take the AIS Tour, 3C, PDF of Tour, 4F, 6A
- Program manuals. (Box 173)
  - Rules of Procedure, 1995 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Running an Effective Meeting, 2001 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Saginaw Steering Gear Division General Motors Management Program Manual Part 1, 1987 (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - Saginaw Steering Division General Motors Management Program Manual Part 2, 1987 (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Salary Administration, 2000 (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - Selection and Staffing (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - Sexual Harassment; It's No Game, 1998 (Box 173, Folder 7)
    Fredda Merton, Center for Women in Gov't, SUNY Albany, April 1998
  - Sexual Harassment Prevention Training, 1998 (Box 173, Folder 8)
  - Shared Visions, 1989 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - SHRM Learning Administrator's Guide, 2002 (Box 173, Folder 10)
  - SHRM Learning System, 2003 (Box 173, Folder 11)
  - SHRM International Practices, 1999 (Box 173, Folder 12)
  - SHRM Online Course Delivery, 1999 (Box 173, Folder 13)
  - SHRM Administrator's Guide, 2001 (Box 173, Folder 14)
  - SHRM Module 1, 2002 (Box 173, Folder 15)
  - SHRM Module 1 Instr., 2002 (Box 173, Folder 16)
  - SHRM Module 2, 2002 (Box 173, Folder 17)
  - SHRM Module 2 Instr., 2002 (Box 173, Folder 18)
  - SHRM Module 3, 2002 (Box 173, Folder 19)
  - SHRM Module 3 Instr., 2002 (Box 173, Folder 20)
  - SHRM Module 4, 2002 (Box 173, Folder 21)
  - SHRM Module 4 Instr., 2002 (Box 173, Folder 22)
    Contains CD Labeled PowerPoint Slides
  - SHRM Module 5, 2002 (Box 173, Folder 23)
  - SHRM Module 6, 2002 (Box 173, Folder 24)
  - SHRM Module 6 Instr., 2002 (Box 173, Folder 25)
- Program manuals. (Box 174)
  - Railway Labor Studies Part 1, 1975 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - Railway Labor Studies Part 2, 1975 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - Railway Labor Studies Part 3, 1975 (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - Recent Developments, 2001 (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - Recent Developments before NLRB Part 1 Ver. 1, 2003 (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - Recent Developments before NLRB Part 2 Ver. 1, 2003 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - Recent Developments before NLRB Part 1 Ver. 2, 2003 (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - Recent Developments before NLRB Part 2 Ver. 2, 2003 (Box 174, Folder 8)
  - Recent Developments before NLRB, 2004 (Box 174, Folder 9)
  - Resource Manual Leading in a Quality Environment, 1993 (Box 174, Folder 10)
  - Resource Manual Leading in a Quality Environment, 1994 (Box 174, Folder 11)
  - Resource Manual Leadership and Team Building, 1991 (Box 174, Folder 12)
  - Resource Manual: Some Tips, 1991 (Box 174, Folder 13)
  - Resources for Workplace Diversity, 1996 (Box 174, Folder 14)
  - Resources for Workplace Diversity, 2000 (Box 174, Folder 15)
  - Retirement Preparation Program: Niagara Frontier Industry Education Council, 1976 (Box 174, Folder 16)
    NFIEC: A Cooperative Effort of Business, Education, Industry, and Labor
  - Revolutions in Europe, 1990 (Box 174, Folder 17)
  - Rochester Products UAW Local 1097 Part 1 Ver. 1, 1992 (Box 174, Folder 18)
  - Rochester Products UAW Local 1097 Part 2 Ver. 1, 1992 (Box 174, Folder 19)
  - Rochester Products UAW Local 1097 Part 1 Ver. 2, 1997 (Box 174, Folder 20)
  - Rochester Products UAW Local 1097 Part 2 Ver. 2, 1997 (Box 174, Folder 21)
- Program Files- Credit Grad. Student, BLS. (Box 175)
  - Public Sector Labor Law (245), 1992 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    Buffalo Labor Studies, 91W116, 1/22-4/8/1992, Poch
  - Contemporary Labor Problems (015), 1992 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    Buffalo Labor Studies, 91W122, 4/29-6/3/1992, MacPherson
  - Work Organization and Troubled Employees (044), 1992 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    Buffalo Labor Studies, 91W123, 4/29-6/3/1992, Mangino
  - Buffalo Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Project Surveys, 1991 (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Project Surveys, 1991 (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - Labor Relations Law and Legislation (501), 1991 (Box 175, Folder 7)
    Graduate Studies Certificate Program, 91W106, 9/26-12/19/1991, Schmit, J.
  - Case Studies in Personnel Administration (665), 1991 (Box 175, Folder 8)
    Graduate Studies Certificate Program, 91W107, 9/24-12/17/1991, Smith, C.
  - Instructor Memos- Book Orders, 1991 (Box 175, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Studies, Winter, 1992 (Box 175, Folder 10)
    Contains several folders: Flier Mailing, Press Releases, Kenan CTR, Registrations, Memos to Students, Attendance/Grade Sheets
  - Collective Bargaining (202-500), 1992 (Box 175, Folder 11)
    Graduate Studies Certificate Program, 91W124, 1/8-3/25/1992, Smith
  - Labor Relations Law and Legislation, 1992 (Box 175, Folder 12)
    Graduate Studies Certificate Program, 91W125, 1/7-3/24/1992, Campagna
  - Graduate Studies, Spring, 1992 (Box 175, Folder 13)
    Contains several folders: Flier Mailing, Press Releases, Kenan CTR, Registrations, Attendance, Memos to Students, Instructor Memos
  - Arbitration (202-602), 1992 (Box 175, Folder 14)
    Graduate Studies Certificate Program, 91W126, 4/1-6/24/1992, Bantle
  - Graduate Project Surveys, 1991-1993 (Box 175, Folder 15)
  - Graduate Studies, Fall, 1991 (Box 175, Folder 16)
    Contains several folders: Flier Mailing, Attendance, Memos to Students, Press Releases, Kenan CTR, Registrations, Instructor Memos
  - Human Resource Economics and Public Policy, 1992 (Box 175, Folder 17)
    Graduate Studies Certificate Program, 91W127, 3/31-6/23/1992, Davis
  - Graduate Studies, Fall, 1992 (Box 175, Folder 18)
    Contains several folders: Flier Mailing, Press Releases, Kenan CTR, Instructor Memo, Student Memo, Registration
  - Performance Appraisal and Productivity Improvement (663), 1992 (Box 175, Folder 19)
    Graduate Studies Program, 92W115, 9/9-12/2/1992, Morano
  - Case Studies in Personnel Administration (665), 1992 (Box 175, Folder 20)
    Graduate Studies Program, 92W114, 9/10-12/3/1992, Smith
- Program manuals. (Box 176)
  - PEL Master Copy- Nell Hamilton Part 1, 1989 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - PEL Master Copy- Nell Hamilton Part 2, 1989 (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Planning for Successful Living, UAW Retired and Older Workers Dept., 1980 (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - Political Action for Unionists, 1996 (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - Portable Conference on Change Management Part 1, 1997 (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - Portable Conference on Change Management Part 2, 1997 (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - Preparation for Collective Bargaining, Fall, Ver. 1, 1997 (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - Preparation for Collective Bargaining, Fall, Ver. 2, 1997 (Box 176, Folder 8)
  - Preparation for Collective Bargaining, 1998 (Box 176, Folder 9)
  - Preparation for Collective Bargaining Part 1, 1999 (Box 176, Folder 10)
  - Preparation for Collective Bargaining Part 2, 1999 (Box 176, Folder 11)
  - Preparation for Collective Bargaining, 1999 (Box 176, Folder 12)
  - Preventing Sexual Harassment, Scott Aviation, 1997 (Box 176, Folder 13)
  - Preventing Sexual Harassment, Scott Aviation, 1998 (Box 176, Folder 14)
  - Preventing Sexual Harassment, 1997 (Box 176, Folder 15)
  - Preventing Sexual Harassment, 1999 (Box 176, Folder 16)
  - Preventing Sexual Harassment in the Workplace, 2000 (Box 176, Folder 17)
  - Problem Solving through Mutual Gains, 2000 (Box 176, Folder 18)
  - Process Improvement and Facilitation Tools Resource Manual, 1994 (Box 176, Folder 19)
  - Promoting Employee Recognition, 1997 (Box 176, Folder 20)
  - Quality: Working in the Auto Industry, 1995 (Box 176, Folder 21)
  - Quality Handouts, 1995 (Box 176, Folder 22)
  - Quality in the Public Sector: Training, 1994 (Box 176, Folder 23)
  - Quality in the Public Sector: Implementation Model, 1994 (Box 176, Folder 24)
  - Railway Labor Course Part 1, 1990 (Box 176, Folder 25)
  - Railway Labor Course Part 2, 1990 (Box 176, Folder 26)
- Program manuals. (Box 177)
  - Managerial Process Analysis Part 1, 1966 (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - Managerial Process Analysis Part 2, 1966 (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - Managing Crisis, 1998 (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - Marketing of Public Workshops, 1998 (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - Master Labor Relations Law, 1998 (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - Measuring Training and Performance, 1997 (Box 177, Folder 6)
  - Mediating Employment Disputes Part 1, 1999 (Box 177, Folder 7)
  - Mediating Employment Disputes Part 2, 1999 (Box 177, Folder 8)
  - Mediation II, 2001 (Box 177, Folder 9)
  - Mediation of Employment Disputes Part 1, 1999 (Box 177, Folder 10)
  - Mediation of Employment Disputes Part 2, 1999 (Box 177, Folder 11)
  - Mutual Aid, 1999 (Box 177, Folder 12)
  - Mutual Gains Negotiating (Box 177, Folder 13)
  - Mutual Gains Bargaining (Negotiation), 1996 (Box 177, Folder 14)
    97W170, 5/22-23/1996
  - Mutual Gains Negotiation, 1997 (Box 177, Folder 15)
  - Mutual Gains Negotiation, 1998 (Box 177, Folder 16)
  - Mutual Gains Negotiation Symposium, 1994 (Box 177, Folder 17)
  - Negotiating a Healthy Future, 2002 (Box 177, Folder 18)
  - Netter Labor-Management Part 1 Ver. 1, 1994 (Box 177, Folder 19)
  - Netter Labor-Management Part 2 Ver. 1, 1994 (Box 177, Folder 20)
  - New Managerial Work: Supervisory Training, 1990 (Box 177, Folder 21)
    For the Non-Hierarchical Organization
  - New Opportunities for Cont. Education Responding to the Changing Economy Part 1, 1988 (Box 177, Folder 22)
  - New Opportunities for Cont. Education Responding to the Changing Economy Part 2, 1988 (Box 177, Folder 23)
  - NYS Workers' Compensation, 1998 (Box 177, Folder 24)
  - OAB Local 593 Presentation Notes (Box 177, Folder 25)
  - Training Program for One on One Coordinators (Box 177, Folder 26)
  - Part I: Introduction to Mediation (Box 177, Folder 27)
  - Partners for the 21st Century, 1997 (Box 177, Folder 28)
- Program Files-Credit, SS. (Box 178)
  - Supervisory and Graduate Studies, 1994 (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - Collective Bargaining in the Public Sector, 1994 (Box 178, Folder 2)
    Graduate Studies, 93W133, 3/29-6/21/94, Campagna/Poch
  - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 178, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence and Press Releases, 1994 (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - Ithaca and BMH Correspondence, 1994 (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - Workers in the Global Economy, Oral Communications, and Intro to Financial Management, 1994 (Box 178, Folder 6)
    (MYV)
  - Supervisory Studies, 1994 (Box 178, Folder 7)
    Dynamics of Organizational Behavior and Managing Stress in the Workplace
  - BLS- Maryvale, 1995 (Box 178, Folder 8)
    Labor in the American Economy, Analyzing Issues that Divide American Workers, Labor Law II
  - Oral Communication (210-083-03), 1995 (Box 178, Folder 9)
    Supervisory Studies, 94W138, 4/6-6/1/95, Hall
  - Supervisory Studies, 1995 (Box 178, Folder 10)
    Dynamics of Organizational Behavior and Oral Communications
  - Managing Stress in the Workplace, 1995 (Box 178, Folder 11)
    Supervisory Studies, Spring, Brady
  - Stress Management in the Workplace (210-002-01), 1995 (Box 178, Folder 12)
    Supervisory Studies, 94W143, 4/6-6/1/95, Brady
  - Ithaca and SS Correspondence, 1995 (Box 178, Folder 13)
    Contains Course; Principles of Supervision
  - Contract Administration (200-253-02), 1995 (Box 178, Folder 14)
    Labor Studies (MYV), 94W135, 1/24-4/11/95, Jurenovich
  - Principles and Practices of Management II, 1995 (Box 178, Folder 15)
    Leadership in Groups, Spring, Grippi
  - Conflict Resolution(210-016-01), 1995 (Box 178, Folder 16)
    Supervisory Studies (MYV), 94W132, 1/10-3/28/95, Ahearn
  - Dynamics of Interpersonal Behavior (210-092), 1995 (Box 178, Folder 17)
    Supervisory Studies (MYV), 94W131, 1/10-3/28/95, Ahearn
  - Supervisory Studies, 1995 (Box 178, Folder 18)
    Principles and Practices of Management II and Dynamics of Organizational Behavior
  - Employee Assistance Program (200-028), 1995 (Box 178, Folder 19)
    Labor Studies (MYV), 94W134, 2/25-3/25-95, Cunningham
  - Dynamics of Interpersonal Behavior (210-092), 1995 (Box 178, Folder 20)
    Supervisory Studies (MYV), 94W129-130, 1/10-3/28/95, Grippi
  - Employee Relations for Supervisors (210-035-03), 1995 (Box 178, Folder 21)
    Supervisory Studies (MYV), 94W126-128, 1/10-3/25/95, Hoelen and Scaccia
- Program manuals. (Box 179)
  - Labor Relations Law Ver. 2, 1998 (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - Labor Management Cooperation, 1998 (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - Law Enforced by the US EEO Commission (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - Leadership Development Program Part 1, 2001 (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - Leadership Development Program Part 2, 2001 (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - Leading in a Quality Environment, 1993 (Box 179, Folder 6)
  - Leading in a Quality Environment Participant, 1993 (Box 179, Folder 7)
  - Leading in a Quality Environment Participant, 1994 (Box 179, Folder 8)
  - Lifestyle Management Legal Services and Benefits, 2000 (Box 179, Folder 9)
  - Lifestyle Management Coordinator's Manual Ver. 1 (Box 179, Folder 10)
  - Lifestyle Management Coordinator's Manual Part 1 Ver. 2, 1994 (Box 179, Folder 11)
  - Lifestyle Management Coordinator's Manual Part 2 Ver. 2, 1994 (Box 179, Folder 12)
  - Lifestyle Management Coordinator's Manual Part 1 Ver. 3, 2004 (Box 179, Folder 13)
  - Lifestyle Management Coordinator's Manual Part 2 Ver. 3, 2004 (Box 179, Folder 14)
  - Lifestyle Management Planning Your Future, 2006 (Box 179, Folder 15)
  - Lifestyle Management Ready or Not, 2002 (Box 179, Folder 16)
  - Lifestyle Management Ready or Not, 2003 (Box 179, Folder 17)
  - Lifestyle Management Ready or Not, 2004 (Box 179, Folder 18)
  - Lighting the Torch for Labor Education, 1986 (Box 179, Folder 19)
  - Local Officers Resource Manual, 1991 (Box 179, Folder 20)
  - Local Paid Educational Leave Part 1 (Box 179, Folder 21)
  - Local Paid Educational Leave Part 2 (Box 179, Folder 22)
  - Making the Difference Part 1 (Box 179, Folder 23)
  - Making the Difference Part 2 (Box 179, Folder 24)
  - Management's Right to Manage, 1968 (Box 179, Folder 25)
- Program Files. H&S - Program no. 2067. (Box 180)
  - Ergonomics Training/Injury Prevention, 2000 (Box 180, Folder 1)
    99C2064-2075
  - Hazard and Operability Analysis, 2000 (Box 180, Folder 2)
    99C2076-2083
  - Public, 2000 (Box 180, Folder 3)
    99C2084-2086
  - Public, Hazard Analysis, Ergonomics, 2000 (Box 180, Folder 4)
    99C2087-2111
  - Enviroscience Consultants, Public, 2000 (Box 180, Folder 5)
    99C2113-2122
  - Public, 2000 (Box 180, Folder 6)
    00C2123-2125
  - Envirohealth, 2000 (Box 180, Folder 7)
    99C2126-2128
  - Emp Improvement in Workplace Health and Safety, Crisis Management, and Safety and Health CMTE Skills, 2000 (Box 180, Folder 8)
    00C2131-2141
  - 99C2129, 2000 (Box 180, Folder 9)
  - 99C2130, 2000 (Box 180, Folder 10)
  - Public and Envotech, 2000 (Box 180, Folder 11)
    00C2144-2148 and April Lead Programs
- Faculty Team. Fleron, Dir. -Institute for Industry Studies. (Box 181)
  - PEL Auto Industry Manual (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - PEL Auto Industry Manual (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - PEL Auto Industry Manual (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - PEL Auto Industry Manual (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - PEL Auto Industry Manual (Box 181, Folder 5)
  - PEL Auto Industry Manual (Draft) (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - Auto Industry Manual Readings (Box 181, Folder 7)
  - Labor Calendars, 1985 (Box 181, Folder 8)
- Program Files. H&S - Program no. 2395-2463. (Box 182)
  - Crisis Prevention and Management, Stress Management, 2002 (Box 182, Folder 1)
    Contains 5 folders: Stress-Rochester, Crisis-Albany, Stress- Albany, Crisis-Ithaca, Stress-Ithaca
  - Crisis Prevention and Management, Stress Management, 2002 (Box 182, Folder 2)
    Contains 5 folders: Crisis-L.I., Stress-L.I., Crisis and Stress- Rollins College, USPS Union, MCWA Crisis Prevention Proposal
  - Supervisor, Train the Trainer, Safe Work Practices, Global Metallurgical, 2001-2002 (Box 182, Folder 3)
    Contains 10 folders: Lead Abatement Sup./Contr., Labor Law II-OSHA, Safe Work Practices [2], Train the Trainer [2], Globe Metallurgical [4]
  - Globe Metallurgical, Crisis Prevention and Stress Management, 2001-2002 (Box 182, Folder 4)
    Contains 13 folders: Globe Metallurgical [3], Milward Alloys, Stress, Globe-Respiratory Prot. [6], Crisis Management Strategy, Crisis Response Plan
  - Public, 2001 (Box 182, Folder 5)
    Contains 2 folders: Lead Inspector and Risk Assessor (01C2436-7)
  - MCWA- Hazcom and PPE, and M.I. and Training, 1994 (Box 182, Folder 6)
    Contains 2 folders: PPE and Training
  - Health and Safety, 2001-2002 (Box 182, Folder 7)
    Contains 7 folders: SHRM, BBP and TB, What it's Like to be a CIH [4], CCFL/Corning
  - Crisis Management and Ripley IAQ, 2002 (Box 182, Folder 8)
    Contains 7 folders: Crisis Management [3], Unions and War on Terrorism, Ripley- IAQ- Classroom Trng, Crisis Prgm.
  - Chemical Hazard-Vesuvius, 2002 (Box 182, Folder 9)
    Contains 4 folders: Chemical Hazard- Vesuvius [4]
- Faculty -Rebholz, Yonnve. (Box 183)
  - Extension Meetings, 1991 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Extension Labor Calendar, 1993 (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - Extension Programs in Buffalo, 1990 (Box 183, Folder 3)
    Contains Pins and Brochures
  - Employment Relations (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - Employee Assistance Education and Research Program, 1989 (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - Empire State College, 1998 (Box 183, Folder 6)
  - Empire State College, 1974 (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - Elgie, Donna, 1997 (Box 183, Folder 8)
  - Empire State College Brochures (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - Elections and Nominations Comm, 1988-1989 (Box 183, Folder 10)
  - Destination: Buffalo, 1999 (Box 183, Folder 11)
  - Extension Directors Meeting, 1999 (Box 183, Folder 12)
  - Disclosure Statements, 2002-2003 (Box 183, Folder 13)
  - Distance Learning, 1997 (Box 183, Folder 14)
  - Destination: Buffalo, 1997 (Box 183, Folder 15)
  - Buffalo Labor Studies, 1991 (Box 183, Folder 16)
  - Damon and Morey (Box 183, Folder 17)
  - CWA, 1995 (Box 183, Folder 18)
  - Maurice Curlee, 2001 (Box 183, Folder 19)
  - CSEA/LEAP (Box 183, Folder 20)
  - Catalog, 1986-1987 (Box 183, Folder 21)
  - Credit Programs- General, 1994 (Box 183, Folder 22)
  - Credit Committee, 1995 (Box 183, Folder 23)
  - Course Info- CIT, 2002 (Box 183, Folder 24)
  - Cornell Facts, 1997-1998 (Box 183, Folder 25)
  - Coop Extension Marketing, 1992 (Box 183, Folder 26)
  - Alice Cook, 1998 (Box 183, Folder 27)
  - Employment, Workplace Practices and Labor-Management Relations in Western NY (Box 183, Folder 28)
  - CEU's, 1998 (Box 183, Folder 29)
  - Central Europe HR Education Initiative, 1995-1996 (Box 183, Folder 30)
  - Center for Competitiveness, 1997 (Box 183, Folder 31)
  - Certificates, 1989 (Box 183, Folder 32)
  - Cellular One, 2000 (Box 183, Folder 33)
  - Carney, 2002 (Box 183, Folder 34)
    5/10/02
  - Catherwood, 1997 (Box 183, Folder 35)
  - Campbell, Reszka, 1993 (Box 183, Folder 36)
  - Campagna, Rachel, 2002 (Box 183, Folder 37)
  - Campagna, Project Labor Agreements, 1997 (Box 183, Folder 38)
  - Calendars, 1983-1986 (Box 183, Folder 39)
- Program Files. MGMT 96W175-97W037. (Box 184)
  - Lecture on Grievance/Arbitration, 1997 (Box 184, Folder 1)
    State Teachers College, 96W175, 2/26/97, Campagna
  - The Value and Strength of Diversity, 1997 (Box 184, Folder 2)
    Auto Alliance International, 96W176, 3/20/97, Murak
  - The Value and Strength of Diversity, 1997 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    Auto Alliance International, Inc., 96W177, 5/1/97, Henderson
  - The Value and Strength of Diversity, 1997 (Box 184, Folder 4)
    Auto Alliance International, Inc., 96W178-180, 5/1, 15, 22, 29/97, Henderson
  - The Value and Strength of Diversity, 1997 (Box 184, Folder 5)
    Auto Alliance International, Inc., 96W181-183, 6/5, 12, 19/97, Henderson
  - Diversity in the Workplace, 1997 (Box 184, Folder 6)
    Greater Buffalo Partnership, 96W184, 4/23/97, Henderson
  - Strategic Implementation: Vision in Progress, 1997 (Box 184, Folder 7)
    OAB- Local 593, 96W185, 4/28/97, Fleron
  - Making Differences Work, 1997 (Box 184, Folder 8)
    Buffalo Science Museum, 96W186, 6/26/97, Henderson
  - Sexual Harassment: Management Session, 1997 (Box 184, Folder 9)
    Buffalo Science Museum, 96W186, 5/14/97, Henderson
  - Workplace Diversity: Management Session, 1997 (Box 184, Folder 10)
    Buffalo Science Museum, 96W186, 5/17/97, Woods
  - Acquisitions and Privatization, 1997 (Box 184, Folder 11)
    Health Care Mergers, 96W188, 6/17/97, Campagna, eta
  - The Value and Strength of People, 1997 (Box 184, Folder 12)
    Auto Alliance International, Inc., 96W189-190, 4/17/97, Mural
  - Mutual Gains Negotiation in Education, 1997 (Box 184, Folder 13)
    Buffalo Board of Education, 96W191, 4/22-23/97, Martin et al
  - Mutual Gains Negotiation, 1997 (Box 184, Folder 14)
    Cornell University, 96W192, 6/12-13/97, Woods
  - Diversity Workshop, 1997 (Box 184, Folder 15)